We'll guide you through how to connect
internet from mobile to a laptop using a
USB cable. If you find this useful, then
consider subscribing and liking the
video.
This is convenient to do as you see at
the moment I'm not currently connected
to the internet on the laptop and I want
to be able to so I can browse it. So,
what we're going to do is we're going to
go and grab the cable. We're going to go
and plug one end into the laptop so we
can go and plug it in just over here.
Then after you've gone and plugged it in
with the lap with the laptop, you grab
the other end and you want to go and
have the phone unlocked. And what we're
going to do is we're going to go and
plug it in. You should go and see that
it will go and start charging. Now you
want to go and drag down like this. You
need to go and find USB 4 and go and tap
there.
Make sure it's set to transferring files
or USB tethering. Next, go and swipe up
on your device. And then what you need
to do is come to your settings. You want
to go and find the option for
connections
and you want to go down to mobile
hotspot and tethering
and you want to switch on USB tethering.
Share your phone's internet connection
using a USB cable. Switch it on
and shortly you're going to go and see
it will go and change to connected on
the laptop. We're now connected. Leave a
like if you found this useful.